

Las Vegas, Nevada (831) 920-8858 wle831@gmail.com

about me

Experienced Help Desk Technician with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology industry.

I love the outdoors. I attempted a 2,200 mile thru-hike of the Appalachian Trail in 2020 but had to throw in the towel after the coronavirus pandemic closed down the eastern seaboard.

I am obsessed with technology. I have Cisco routers & switches in my house. I configured a high speed wireless network in the middle of nowhere using LTE and yagi antennas. I am a true grinder and love new opportunities to learn and expand my horizons.

I moved to Las Vegas to escape the California wildfires that literally destroyed my entire community.

History

Prime Trust LLC., Las Vegas, NV — Help Desk / Desktop Support Technician

AUG 20 - PRESENT

Configure Inc., San Jose, CA — *Network Operations Center Technician*

MAR 2018 - MARCH 2019

U.S. Army, Fort Hood, TX — Police Officer

OCT 2004 - MAR 2014

Education

Hartnell College, Salinas, CA — *Computer Science/IT* JAN 2014 - 2018

Skills

PC Hardware

Windows 10

Linux

Networking (Cisco)

AWS

Microsoft Office

Graphic Imaging



Google IT Professional

CompTIA A+

Hardware 901